Erikas Taroza

PROFILE

I am an experienced software developer with a diverse set of skills including Flutter/Dart, web development, Git, and Linux. My journey in software development is marked by my drive to constantly grow my skills and my commitment to excellence. I am also an active contributor to the open-source community. I maintain my own projects as well as help fix various bugs in other open-source projects.

EXPERIENCE

January 2023 - Present

Full Stack Developer, IDMSRTV (Startup)

- Implemented core functionality of product
- Drove strategy for website development
- Identified and implemented modern technologies to get the beta website to market faster
- Collaborated with cross functional team leaders to define project scope and timelines
- Rewrote WordPress website with improved styling and functionality
- Frameworks/languages used
 - Angular
 - Vue
 - Java (Android app)
 - Rust
 - o PHP
 - WordPress

October 2022 - December 2022 Intern Web Developer, Deidis (Startup)

- Developed widget to provide clients an easy way to capture leads
- · Frameworks/languages used
 - React
 - NodeJS

ACHIEVEMENTS

Google Cloud Certified

Google Cloud Associate Cloud Engineer (2023)

See Certificate

PROJECTS

October 2022 - Present

simple_audio

- A simple cross-platform solution for playing audio in Flutter
- Rust
- Open source

May 2022 - Present

BitBeat

- Music streaming app with no ads
- Docker
- Frameworks/languages used
 - Flutter
 - Vue
 - Rust

December 2020 - Present

Open Source

Contributing to open source projects by fixing issues, adding new features, or creating my own open source projects.

See my work here: https://github.com/erikas-taroza

June 2016 - July 2020

Multiplayer Game Development

- 2D platformer
- Unity 5 Unity 2019
- Unreal Engine 4

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Cloud	Frontend	Backend	Languages
GCPAWSVultr	FlutterVue	Express.jsMySQLSurrealDBAxumParse Server	 Dart JavaScript TypeScript Rust C# Java Python

EDUCATION

July 2019 - January 2023 Laurel Springs School

High School

- 3.75 GPA (3.90 weighted)
- AP Computer Science (4/5 on AP exam)

July 2016 - Present Self-Taught

I taught myself everything I know about programming.